Finding aid for the R.B. Kitaj papers LSC.1741
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 8. Personal Correspondence, 1951-2007; 52 boxes
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Bishop, Isabel (2 of 2), 1980 - 1984; 21 items. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Blake, Peter, 1974 - 1980; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Blankfort, Ellie, 1976; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Blankfort, Michael and Dorothy [Dossy], 1963 - 1970; 20 items. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Blankfort, Michael and Dorothy [Dossy], 1971 - 1990; 56 items. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Blitz, Nelson, 1980 - 1984; 7 items. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Bloom, Claire, undated; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Botelho, Manuel, 1994; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Bowling, Frank, 1987 - 1996; 8 items. (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Boyle, Richard [Dick], 1981 - 1994; 6 items. (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Bradford, Matías Serra, 2007; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Bramley-Moore, Mostyn, 1981 - 1982; 4 items. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Brant, Bill, 1981; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Brennan, Walter, 1969; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Breverman, Harvey, 1994; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Brighton, Andrew, 1976 - 1989; 14 items. (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Bromberg, Ruth, 1987 - 2000; 7 items. (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Brookner, Anita, undated; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Brooks, Ruthie and Ray, 1980 - 1985; 5 items. (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Brouwers, Emmelien, undated; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Brown, Jonathan, 1974; 4 items. (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Brubaker, Jeanne, 1981 - 1995; 6 items. (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Buck, Paul, 1974 - 1978; 5 items. (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Buckley, Stephen, 1975 - 1986; 16 items. (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Burns, Rodney, 1975 - 1976; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Burroughs, William and Ian Lang, 1986; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Burt, Dan, 2001; 2 items. (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Caddel, Richard, 1996; 5 items. (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Calhoun, Douglas, 1972 - 1973; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Camiel, Naftali, 1989 - 1995; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Camp, Jeffery, undated; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Campbell, Robin, undated; 3 items. (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Caris, Gerard, 1968 - 1990; 11 items. (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Carlisle, Isabel, 1996 - 1998; 4 items. (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Caro, Anthony, 1979 - 1981; 2 items. (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Carrier, David, 1974 - 1999; 15 items. (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Casey, Thornton, 1967 - 1977; 5 items. (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Caulfield, Patrick, 1964; 4 items. (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Cavat, Irma, undated; 2 items. (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Clair, Jean, 1977 - 1983; 9 items. (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Clark, Thomas, undated; 2 items. (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - Claxton, Julia, 1992 - 2001; 24 items. (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - Clothier, Peter, 1979 - 2003; 7 items. (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Clute, Judith, 1994 - 1997; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Cohen, Becky, 1977 - 2005; 6 items. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Cohen, David, 1986 - 2003; 20 items. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Harold, 1968; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Collins, Hannah, 1977; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Cook, Richard, 1977 - 2003; 11 items. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Cook, Roger, undated; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Cooney, Seamus, 1971, 1974; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Coover, Robert, 1965 - 1985; 12 items. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Corman, Gene, 1986; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Creeley, Penelope, 1983 - 1985; 4 items. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1965 - 1985, 2006; 34 items. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Creffield, Dennis, 1980 - 1996; 16 items. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Cumming, Robert, 1987 - 1989; 8 items. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Cutts, Simon, 1978 - 1996; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Daley, Janet, 1977 - 1985; 7 items. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Dannheisser, Hans, 1995 - 2003; 16 items. (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Danowski, Raymond, no date; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Dark, Christopher, 1994; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Davies, Hugh, 1978 - 1984; 4 items. (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Davies, John, 1999; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Bill, 1963; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - de Botton, Gilbert and Jacqueline, 1987 - 1996; 21 items. (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - de Francia, Peter, 1963 - 1990; 48 items. (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Dehoff, Ruth, 1991 - 1995; 7 items. (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Delevante, Sidney, 1957 - 1977; 19 items. (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Denny, Robyn, 1990; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Deppner, Martin, 1978 - 1997; 32 items. (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Diebenkorn, Richard, 1972 - 1991; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - di Stefano, Arturo, 1981 - 1997; 7 items. (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Doisneau, Robert, 1989; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Donlevy, Brian, 1975; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Dorn, Ed, 1966 - 1967; 4 items. (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Dowling, Paddy, 1976 - 1990; 13 items. (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Drew, Joanna, 1979 - 1989; 13 items. (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Dubovsky, Anthony, 1978 - 2005; 4 items. (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Dubsky, Mario, 1981 - 1984; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Dufort, Anthony, 1976; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1980 - 1984, 2006; 16 items. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Duncan, Robert and Jess Collins, 1967 - 1979; 38 items. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Dunlop, Ian, 1981; 3 items. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Edelstein, Mel and Eleanor, 1971 - 2000; 11 items. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Epstein, John, undated; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Eshelman, Clayton and Caryl, 1971 - 1999; 28 items. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Eveleigh, Aldous, 1991; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Farthing, Stephen, 1990; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Feaver, William (Bill), 1990 - 2003; 6 items. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Fein, Richard, 1994 - 2004; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Feldman, Morton, 1967 - 1968; 8 items. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Felver, Christopher, 1990; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Field, Richard, 1971, 1980; 4 items. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Finchas, Anna, undated; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Finer, Stephen, 1981 - 1997; 26 items. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Finnigan, John Temple, 1993; 4 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Fischer, Harry, 1961 - 1971; 34 items. (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Fisher, Allen, 1987; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Fisher, Ethel, 1974 - 2005; 13 items. (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Fisher, Gene, 1989 - 1995; 11 items. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Fisher, Margaret, 1982 - 2006; 35 items. (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Flor, Harald, 1990 - 2007; 13 items. (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Forge, Andrew, 1970 - 1982; 9 items. (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Forrest, Bernard, 1968 - 1970; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Foye, Raymond, 1977 - 1986; 14 items. (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Frajndlich, Abe, 1981; 3 items. (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Frankel, Ari, 1994 - 1999; 3 items. (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Frankel, William and Claire, 1984 - 1995; 8 items. (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Freed, David, 1975 - 2006; 29 items. (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Friedlander, Rabbi Albert, 1985 - 1997; 16 items. (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Friedlander, Lee and Maria (1 of 3), 1971 - 1989; 44 items. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Friedlander, Lee and Maria (2 of 3), 1970 - 1989; 29 items. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Friedlander, Lee and Maria (3 of 3), 1970 - 1991; 29 items. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Friedlander, Maria, 1983 - 2007; 19 items. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Frued, Lucian, 1982 - 1992; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Fuller, Peter, 1980 - 1989; 15 items. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Furnival, John, 1964; 2 items. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Gablik, Suzi, 1966 - 1984; 24 items. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Gardner, Edward, 1984 - 2006; 9 items. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Gardner, Ian, 1975 - 1976; 3 items. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Geldzahler, Henry, 1981; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Gifford, Barry, 2005; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Gilbert, Martin, 1982 - 2000; 12 items. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Gildzen, Alex, 1971 - 1996; 51 items. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Gili, Katherine, 1986 - 1994; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Gilmour, Pat, 1974 - 1992; 6 items. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1979; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Glaser, Rabbi Joseph, 1981 - 1982; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Gold, Joan, 1991; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Golding, John, 1975 - 1992; 35 items. (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Goldstein, William (Bill), 1967 - 1994; 21 items. (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Goldwyn, Samuel, 1981 - 1982; 3 items. (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Gooding, Mel, 1991, 1992; 2 items. (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Gouk, Alan, 1969 - 1992; 4 items. (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Goulds, Peter, 1979 - 1996; 21 items. (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Gowrie, Grey, 1988 - 1990; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Grady, James, 1969; 2 items. (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Graham, John, 1961; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Graham, Stephen, 1966 - 1969; 7 items. (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Greene, Leslie, 1984 - 1986; 4 items. (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy, 1990; 2 items. (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Greenstone, Marion, 1963 - 1993; 26 items. (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Grey, Joel, 1973 - 2007; 17 items. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Grooms, Red, 1981; 1 item. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Guirey, Selima, 1983 - 1995; 5 items. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Guston, Philip, 1974; 1 item. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Hambling, Maggi, 1977 - 1988; 4 items. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Hamburger, Michael, 1966 - 1985; 7 items. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, Richard, 1966 - 1984; 28 items. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Hammacher-Van den Brande, Renilde, 1974 - 1983; 6 items. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Hannah, Duncan, 1995 - 1996; 3 items. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Harbutt, Paul, undated; 1 item. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Hargrove, Jim, 1991 - 1996; 3 items. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Hawkins, Bobbie (Creeley), 1979 - 1986; 7 items. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Haworth-Booth, Mark, 1980 - 1999; 7 items. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Hennessy, Richard, 1985 - 1993; 10 items. (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Hess, Scott, 1998 - 2002; 4 items. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Hicks, Alistair, 1987 - 2000; 16 items. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Hicks, Rebecca, 1989 - 1994; 3 items. (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Hill, Mike, 1995; 2 items. (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Hillman, Nehama and Peter, 1980 - 1985; 19 items. (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Hobbs, Peter, 1964; 2 items. (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Hockauf, Jürgen, 1995; 2 items. (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Hockney, Laura, 1980; 2 items. (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Hodgson, Joseph, 1987; 5 items. (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Hofstadter, Dan, 1989 - 1990; 5 items. (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Hoglund, Rudy, 1983; 4 items. (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Holborn, Mark, 1982 - 1994; 4 items. (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Honig, Camille, 1966; 2 items. (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Howard, Peter, 1977 - 1989; 5 items. (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Hoyem, Andrew, 1982 - 1992; 10 items. (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Hoyland, John, 1977; 1 item. (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Hubbard, John, 1989 - 1995; 28 items. (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Hyman, James, 1987 - 2007; 21 items. (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Hyman, Judith, 1983 - 2000; 12 items. (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Hyman, Timothy and Judith (1 of 4), 1977 - 2006; 25 items. (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Hyman, Timothy and Judith (2 of 4), 1979 - 1982; 30 items. (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Hyman, Timothy and Judith (3 of 4), 1984 - 1991; 30 items. (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Hyman, Timothy and Judith (4 of 4), 1988 - 1996; 35 items. (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Irwin, Flavia [de Grey], 1995; 2 items. (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Islah, Jafar, 1976 - 1994; 13 items. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Jacklin, Bill and Lesly, 1980 - 1993; 16 items. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Jacoby, Marianne, undated; 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - James, Elmore, 1986; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - James, Merlin, 1993 - 1996; 4 items. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Jeffrey, Richard and Edith, 1961 - 2003; 65 items. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Jencks, Charles, 1984, 1986; 3 items. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Jerome, Carl, 1977; 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1993; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Ellen, 1977; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Robert Flynn, 1988 - 2007; 10 items. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Joll, James, 1973 - 1987; 9 items. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Allen and Janet, 1965 - 1966; 5 items. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Le Roi (Amiri Baraka), 1969; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Jonic, Bettina, undated; 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Joris, Pierre, 1982; 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Josipovici, Gabriel, 1983 - 1994; 21 items. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Junker, Howard, 1999 - 2002; 5 items. (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Kahn, Wolf, 1974 - 1989; 8 items. (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Kant, Harold Sanford, 1982; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Kantor, Israel, 1988; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Kantor, Jordan, 1993 - 1995; 4 items. (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Karel, Russ, 1985 - 1986; 7 items. (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Kassel, Barbara, 1982 - 1988; 17 items. (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Kelly, Jane, 1997; 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Kendall, Richard, 1983 - 2003; 18 items. (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Kenedy, R.C., 1978; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Kermani, David, 1992, 1995; 2 items. (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - King, Basil, 1993 - 1994; 3 items. (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - King, Neal, 1980 - 1983; 5 items. (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - King, Phillip, 1977; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Kinsman, Jane, 1989 - 1993; 3 items. (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Kirkman, James and Clare, 1976 - 2000; 25 items. (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Kitaj, R.B. (1 of 6), 1946 - 1954; 21 items. (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Kitaj, R.B. (2 of 6), 1955 - 1960; 31 items. (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Kitaj, R.B. (3 of 6), 1961 - 1965; 35 items. (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Kitaj, R.B. (4 of 6), 1966 - 1969; 16 items. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Kitaj, R.B. (5 of 6), 1970 - 1976; 18 items. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Kitaj, R.B. (6 of 6), ca. 1951 - 1969; 17 items. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Kitaj, Dominie, 1987 - 1994; 8 items. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Kitaj, Helene, 1952 - 1973; 5 items. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Kitaj, Jeanne (1 of 3), 1959 - 1983; 53 items. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Kitaj, Jeanne (2 of 3), 1984 - 1994; 49 items. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Kitaj, Jeanne (3 of 3), undated; 20 items. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Kitaj, Karma, 1966 - 2007; 34 items. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Kitaj, Lem, 1985 - 2007; 8 items. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Kitaj, Lem and Dominie (1 of 2), 1966 - 1971; 16 items. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Kitaj, Lem and Dominie (2 of 2), 1972 - 1976; 13 items. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Kitaj, Madeleine, 1971 - 1972; 6 items. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Kitaj, Walter, 1967 - 1981; 6 items. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Klapheck, Konrad, 1965; 2 items. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Knechtel, Tom, 1995 - 2003; 4 items. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Koch, Kenneth, 1969 - 1977; 7 items. (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Kollek, Teddy, 1975, 1983; 2 items. (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Korda, Henry, 1991; 1 item. (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Kossoff, Leon, 1980; 6 items. (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Kozloff, Max, 1966 - 1982; 10 items. (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Kraft, Gilman and Ruth, 1991, 1995; 2 items. (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Kramer, Hilton, 2005; 1 item. (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Kraus, Günther, 1961 - 1965; 3 items. (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Kremen, Irwin, 1991 - 1995; 4 items. (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Krempel, Ulrich, 1984 - 1994; 9 items. (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Laderman, Gabriel, 1990 - 1994; 12 items. (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Lambirth, Andrew, 1988 - 2007; 26 items. (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Lampert, Catherine, 1987 - 1995; 8 items. (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Lancaster, Mark, undated; 1 item. (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Landau, David, 1985 - 1997; 12 items. (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Langdon-Davies, Andrew, 1977 - 1986; 6 items. (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Lanterbach, Anni, 1972 - 1994; 6 items. (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Laughlin, James, 1977; 1 item. (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Lawson, Andrew, 1965 - 1980; 6 items. (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Leary, Jay, 1980 - 2003; 7 items. (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Lee, Janie C., 1995; 2 items. (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Leonard, Michael, 1983; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Lerner, Esther, 1973 - 1984; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Lessore, John, 1977 - 1994; 10 items. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Levin, G. Roy, 1978 - 1980; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Levy, Rabbi Abraham, 1983 - 1984; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Leybourne Sprague, Frederick, 1985 - 1986; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Li, Ying Yeung, 1984 - 1990; 5 items. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Lieb, Ruth, 1983; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Lieberman, William (Bill), 1979; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Ligare, David, 1979; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Livingstone, Marco, 1981 - 1996; 28 items. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Lloyd, Barbara, 1975 - 1988; 5 items. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Lloyd, Francis (Frank), 1985 - 1992; 6 items. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Loehle, Alan, 2004 - 2007; 8 items. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Long, M.J., 1974 - 2006; 26 items. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Lubow, Arthur, 1994; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Lucie-Smith, Edward (Ted), 1980 - 1986; 42 items. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Lynton, Norbert, 1989; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Lyons, Mari, 2006; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh (Christopher Grieve), 1965 - 1967; 5 items. (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Mahler, Marina, 1991; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Mahoney, J.W., 1990 - 1995; 16 items. (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Malynowsky, R. W., 1966 - 1972; 5 items. (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Manser, Leonard, 1980; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Marcus, Penelope, 1979 - 1982; 5 items. (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Marshall, Lauriston, 1979 - 1983; 12 items. (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Martin, John, 1968 - 1986; 4 items. (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Martinet, Jan, 1969, 1981; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Marynka [Watts], 1982 - 1996; 26 items. (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Mason, Emily, 1982; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Mason, Raymond, 1991, 1998; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Massey, Anna, undated; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Masurovsky, Gregory, 1995; 1 item. (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Mathiesen, Niels, 1957 - 1999; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Matoff, Theo, 2001 - 2002; 7 items. (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Maude-Roxby, Roddy, 1995; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - McAlister, Peter, 1966 - 1981; 7 items. (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - McCleary, Dan, 1995 - 2005; 9 items. (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - McClure, Michael, 1969 - 1982; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - McCully, Marilyn, 1997; 3 items. (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - McEwen, John, 1993 - 2002; 4 items. (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - McEwen, Rory, 1970 - 1982; 5 items. (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - McGarrell, James, 1968 - 2002; 7 items. (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - McHenry, Barnabas and Bannon, 1986 - 1994; 6 items. (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Medley, Robert, 1966 - 1992; 18 items. (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Melchert, James and Mary Ann, 1979 - 2002; 16 items. (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Melville, Robert, 1963, no date; 2 items. (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Merians, Elaine and Melvin (Mel), 1986 - 2005; 12 items. (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Merkin, Richard, 1965 - 1982; 38 items. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Metzenbaum, Howard, 1982; 2 items. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Meyer, Joshua, 2006; 3 items. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Middlebrook, Douglas, 1999; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Miles, Jack (John), 1998; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Moffatt, Alexander (Sandy), 1973 - 2001; 22 items. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Monnington, Sir Thomas, 1975; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Morgan, Elmore, 1967 - 1995; 8 items. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Morphet, Richard, 1970 - 1995; 26 items. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Morris, Lynda, 1976 - 1980; 5 items. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Moser, Hannah, 1990; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Mottram, Eric, 1975 - 1988; 7 items. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Mulder, Fredrick, 1977 - 1987; 5 items. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Myers, David and Nomi, 2001 - 2007; 21 items. (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Navaretta, Emmanuel, 1966 - 1972; 4 items. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Nel, Karel, undated; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - O'Conor Barrett, Oliver, 1965; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Oliver, Garth and Fiz, 1972 - 1998; 29 items. (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Oxlade, Roy, 1986 - 1996; 4 items. (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Padgett, Ron, 1970; 7 items. (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Palmer, Michael, 2000 - 2001; 2 items. (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Penrose, Roland, 1972 - 1975; 5 items. (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Pepiatt, Michael and Alice, 1963 - 1996; 21 items. (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Perl, Jed, 1988 - 2005; 16 items. (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Phillips, Adam, 2006; 11 items. (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Phillips, Tom and Jill, 1964 - 2007; 30 items. (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Pickard, Connie, no date; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Plante, David, 1981 - 1992; 17 items. (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Platschek, Hans, 1983; 7 items. (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Posner, David, 1969 - 1978; 30 items. (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Powell, Michael and Thelma Shoonmaker, 1974 - 1991; 30 items. (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Prater, Rose and Chris, 1964 - 1978; 23 items. (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Procktor, Patrick, 1964 - 1985; 5 items. (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Rakosi, Carl, 1979, 1980; 2 items. (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Ramos, Mel, undated; 1 item. (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Ramson, Sidsel, 1969 - 1988; 3 items. (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Rand, Archie, 1989 - 2006; 9 items. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Reddi, Tara, 2001 - 2005; 6 items. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Reichardt, Jasia, 1966 - 1971; 8 items. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Reichardt, Tony, 1970 - 1978; 10 items. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Reicheck, Jesse, 1976, 1977; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Reisman, Celia, 1981 - 2000; 13 items. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Rhoades, Geoffrey, 1965 - 1971; 3 items. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Rhoades, Peter, 1975 - 1994; 21 items. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Rifkind, Robert Gore, 1988, 1995; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Rios, Julian (1 of 2), 1980 - 1997; 42 items. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Rios, Julian (2 of 2), 1980 - 1997; 43 items. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Robb, Carole, 2006; 3 items. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Robinson, David, 1985 - 1996; 12 items. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Rogoff, Irit Keynan, undated; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Roos, Gabriele, undated; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Rorty, Amelie, 1972; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Rosen, Aaron, 2005; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Rosenberg, Harold, 1960; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Rosenberg, Pierre and Beatrice, 1988; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Rosenkrantz, Linda, 1969 - 1975; 11 items. (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Rosoman, Leonard, 1993; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Alan, 1980 - 1995; 10 items. (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Ross, Mike, undated; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Roth, Frank, 1971; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Rothenstein, Michael, undated; 1 item. (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Rothschild, Hannah, 1994; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Rouve, Pierre, 1966 - 1970; 3 items. (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Rudman, Mark, 1993 - 1994; 6 items. (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Rudolph, Anthony, 1995 - 2002; 52 items. (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Rummonds, Gabriel, 1978 - 1979; 4 items. (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Russell, Carol, 1987 - 1993; 7 items. (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Russell, Peter, 1963 - 1970; 5 items. (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Russell, Vera, 1976 - 1991; 53 items. (Box 51, Folder 33)